Finding Aid for the J. Paul Getty Trust Inventory of Getty Publications, 1954-2013 and undated IA10020
Institutional Records and Archives
- J. Paul Getty Museum, 1954-2000; 2003-2013,; undated; Series I.
  - Meier, Richard, Ada Louise Huxtable, Stephen D. Rountree, and Harold M. Williams Making Architecture: the Getty Center. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2010.IA.01-03)
  - Naef, Weston, ed. In Focus: Carleton Watkins. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - Neer, Richard. T. Corpus Vasorum Antiquorum: Molly and Walter Bareiss Collection: Attic Red-Figured Amphorae, Loutrophoros, Pelikai, Stamnos, Psykter, Hydrai, Oinochoai, Lekythoi, Lekanis (lid), Fragments of Undetermined Closed Shapes, and White-Ground Lekthoi. Malibu: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-24)
  - Schönfeldt, Sybil Gräfin. Orpheus and Eurydice. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-13)
  - Seibold, J. Otto, and Vivian Walsh. Going to the Getty. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-31)
  - Turner, Nicholas, Lee Hendrix, and Carol Plazzotta. European Drawings 3, Catalogue of the Collections. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2010.IA.01-03)
  - Walsh, John and Deborah Gribbon. The J. Paul Getty Museum and Its Collections: a Museum for the New Century. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - Barber, Antonia. Apollo & Daphne: Masterpieces of Greek Mythology. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-22)
  - Cassanelli, Roberto, David Massimiliano, Emidio de Albentiis, and Annie Jaques. Ruins of Ancient Rome: The Drawings of French Architects who won the Prix de Rome 1786-1924. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-23)
  - Corpus Vasorum Antiquorum; Molly and Walter Bareiss Collection: Attic Black-Figured Amphorae, Neck-Amphorae, Kraters, Stamnos, Hydriai, and Fragments of Undetermined Closed Shapes; Fascicule 1. Malibu: 1998. (Box 2011.IA.01-06)
  - A Garden of Roman Verse. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-31)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Chefs-ďœuvre du J. Paul Getty Museum: Sculpture Européenne. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-03)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Masterpieces of the J. Paul Getty Museum: European Sculpture. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-03)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Meisterwerke im J. Paul Getty Museum: Europäische Bildhauerei. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-03)
  - Harris, John, ed. Walker Evans: Signs. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-31)
  - Hirsch, Jeffrey. Seeing the Getty Center: A Souvenir Book. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - Lowry, Bates, and Isabel Barrett Lowry. The Silver Canvas: Daguerreotype Masterpieces from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
  - Moore, Mary B. Corpus Vasorum Antiquorum; Molly and Walter Bareiss Collection: Kantharoi and Kantharoid, Skyphos or Mastoid, Skyphoi, Cups Type A: Bilingual Cups, Red-Figured Cups, Cups Type B, Cups Type C, Stemless Cups, Cups of Uncertain Type, White-Ground Cup, Skyphos in Black Glaze; Fascicule 8 [USA Fascicule 33]. Malibu: 1998. (Box 2011.IA.01-06)
  - Naef, Weston, ed. Man Ray: Photographs in the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
    Series: Part of 3-volume boxed set: In Focus: Photographs from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Other volumes in set: Laslo Moholy-Nagy (1995), Andre Kertesz (1994).
  - Scholten, Frits. Adriaen de Vries: 1556-1626. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-03)
  - Seeing the Getty Center: Buildings and Gardens. Los Angeles, 1998. (Box 1987.IA.04-19)
  - Stoneman, Richard. A Luminous Land: Artists Discover Greece. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-22)
  - Allen, Denise and Syson, Luke. Ercole de' Roberti: The Renaissance in Ferrara. London: 1999. (Box 2010.IA.01-03)
  - Asleson, Robyn, ed.A Passion for Performance: Sarah Siddons and Her Portraitists. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2010.IA.01-04)
  - Baldwin, Gordon, and Judith Keller. NadarWarhol: ParisNewYork: Photography and Fame. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
  - Belloli, Andrea. Exploring World Art. Edited by Shelly Kale. Singapore: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-31)
  - De Bie, Ceciel, and Martjn Leenen. Rembrandt: See and Do Children's Book. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-21)
  - Deal, Joe, Mark Johnstone, Richard Meier, and Weston Naef. Between Nature and Culture: Photographs of the Getty Center by Joe Deal. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-03)
  - Harris, John. 1 to 10 and Back Again: a Getty Counting Book. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-03)
  - Harris, John. The Superhuman Crew: Painting by James Ensor, Lyric by Bob Dylan. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-22)
    Includes audio CD of Bob Dylan's "Desolation Row."
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Alpha and Omega: Voices of the Millennium. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. In Focus: Hill and Adamson. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Capolavori del J. Paul Getty Museum: Fotografie. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Chefs-d'œuvre du J. Paul Getty Museum: Photographies. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Masterpieces of the J. Paul Getty Museum: Photographs. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Masterpieces of the J. Paul Getty Museum: Photographs. [Japanese edition]. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Meisterwerke im J. Paul Getty Museum: Fotografien. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Obras Maestras del J. Paul Getty Museum: Fotografías. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
  - Petrén, Birgitta and Elisabetta Putini. Why are You Calling Me a Barbarian?. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-03)
  - Robertson, Bruce. Marguerite Makes a Book. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
    Signed by Illustrator: Kathryn Hewitt.
  - Schreiber, Toby. Athenian Vase Construction: A Potter's Analysis. Malibu: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-22)
  - Woff, Richard. Bright-Eyed Athena: Stories from Ancient Greece. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-21)
  - Armstrong, Carol. A Degas Sketchbook. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-32)
  - Bailey, Colin B. Jean-Baptiste Greuze: The Laundress. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-32)
  - Baker, Malcolm. Figured in Marble: The Making and Viewing of Eighteenth-Century Sculpture. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-31)
  - Barstow, Kurt. The Gualenghi-d'Este Hours: Art and Devotion in Renaissance Ferrara. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-21)
  - Butts, Barbara, and Lee Hendrix. Painting on Light: Drawings and Stained Glass in the Age of Dürer and Holbein. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-25)
  - Coarelli, Filippo, Gian Luca Gregori, Leonardo Lombardi, Silvia Orlandi, Rossella Rea, and Cinzia Vismara. The Colosseum. Edited by Ada Gabucci. Translated by Mary Becker. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-21)
  - De Puma, Richard.Corpus Vasorum Antiquorum; Etruscan Painted Pottery; Fascicule 9 [USA Fascicule 34]. Malibu: 2000. (Box 2011.IA.01-06)
  - Doty, Mark. Murano: Glass from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
  - A Garden of Greek Verse: Poems of Ancient Greece. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-31)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Greek Vases in the J. Paul Getty Museum, Volume 6. Malibu: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-15)
    Series: Occasional Papers on Antiquities, 9.
  - Harris, John, ed. Walker Evans: Florida. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-32)
  - Haynes, Sybille. Etruscan Civilization: A Cultural History. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-21)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. August Sander: Photographs from the J. Paul Getty Museum.. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Eugène Atget: Photographs from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
  - Kale, Shelly, and Lisa Vihos. My Museum Journal: A Writing and Sketching Book. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-32)
  - Korres, Manolis. The Stones of the Parthenon. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-15)
  - Lyons, Lisa. Departures: 11 Artists at the Getty. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2010.IA.01-03)
  - Ramond, Pierre. Masterpieces of Marquetry: Volume I: From the Beginnings to Louis XIV. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-03)
  - Ramond, Pierre. Masterpieces of Marquetry: Volume II: From the Regénce to the Present Day. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-03)
  - Ramond, Pierre. Masterpieces of Marquetry: Volume III: Outstanding Marqueters. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-03)
  - A Treasury of Psalms. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
    Condition: Dust cover torn in upper left front cover.
  - Bartlett, Robert, ed. Medieval Panorama. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-32)
  - Ciarallo, Anamaria. Gardens of Pompeii. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-15)
  - D'Ambrosio, Antonio. Women and Beauty in Pompeii. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-04)
  - De Carolis, Ernesto. Gods and Heroes in Pompeii. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-15)
  - Filden, Alan, and Joann Fletcher. Alexander the Great: Son of the Gods. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-21)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. The J. Paul Getty Museum Handbook of the Collections. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-15)
  - Grossman, Janet Burnett. Greek Funerary Sculpture: Catalogue of the Collections at the Getty Villa. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-15)
  - Kerisel, Françoise, and Frédérick Manson. Diogenes' Lantern. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-32)
  - Mathews, Thomas F. and Alice Taylor. The Armenian Gospels of Gladzor: The Life of Christ Illuminated. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-04)
  - Keller, Judith. Dorothea Lange: Photographs from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-04)
  - Naef, Weston, ed. Manuel Alvarez Bravo: Photographs from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-04)
  - Naef, Weston, ed. William Henry Fox Talbot: Photographs from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-04)
  - Neressian, Vrej. The Bible: In the Armenian Tradition. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-03)
  - Neressian, Vrej. Treasures from the Ark: 1700 Years of Armenian Christian Art. Los Angeles, 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-15)
  - Pfrommer, Michael. Greek Gold from Hellenistic Egypt. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-32)
  - Syson, Luke, and Dora Thornton. Objects of Virtue: Art in Renaissance Italy. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-24)
  - Teviotdale, Elizabeth. The Stammheim Missal. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-15)
  - True, Marion, and Mary Louise Hart, eds. Studia Varia from the J. Paul Getty Museum, Volume 2. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-32)
    Series: Occasional Papers on Antiquities, 10.
  - Turner, Nicholas. European Drawings: 4: Catalogue of the Collections. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-21)
  - Varone, Antonio. Eroticism in Pompeii. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-15)
    Condition: Cover damaged over title, but still readable.
  - Wilson, Gillian, and Catherine Hess. Summary Catalogue of European Decorative Arts in the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-32)
  - Wittwer, Samuel. A Royal Menagerie: Meissen Porcelain Animals. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-04)
  - Wolf, Gita, and Sirish Rao. Sophocles' Antigone. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-32)
  - Amery, Colin, and Brian Curran Jr. The Lost World of Pompeii. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-04)
  - Aubernas, Sylvie. Gustave Le Gray: 1820-1884. Edited by Gordon Baldwin. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-23)
  - Berman, Patricia G. James Ensor: Christ's Entry into Brussels in 1889. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-04)
  - Carradoni, Francesco. Elementary Instructions for Students of Sculpture. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-04)
  - Cerchiai, Luca, Lorena Jannelli, and Fausto Longo. The Greek Cities of Magna Graecia and Sicily. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-15)
  - Clark, Andrew J., Maya Elston, Mary Louise Hart. Understanding Greek Vases: A Guide to Terms, Styles, and Techniques. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-04)
  - De Bie, Ceciel. My Brother Vincent van Gogh. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-22)
  - De Groot, Arie, Geraldine van Heermstra, Liesbeth M. Helmus, and Michiel C. Plomp. Pieter Saenredam, The Utrecht Work. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-26)
  - Doty, Mark. Seeing Venice: Bellotto's Grand Canal. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-32)
  - Fogelman, Peggy, Peter Fusco, and Marietta Cambareri. Italian and Spanish Sculpture: Catalogue of the J. Paul Getty Museum Collection. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-37)
  - Gabucci, Ada. Ancient Rome: Art, Architecture and History. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-15)
  - Harris, John. Greece! Rome! Monsters! Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-32)
  - Harris, John. Italian Ceramics: Catalogue of the J. Paul Getty Museum Collection. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-15)
  - Kaltsas, Nikolaos. Sculpture in the National Archaeological Museum, Athens. Translated by Dr. David Hardy. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-26)
  - Kaplan, Tobi Levinberg, ed. The J. Paul Getty Museum Handbook of the Antiquities Collection. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-32)
  - Ramond, Pierre. Marquetry. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-04)
  - Sheehan, Sean. Illustrated Encyclopedia of Ancient Greece. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-04)
  - Weschler, Lawrence. Robert Irwin Getty Garden. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-16)
  - Abulafia, David, ed. The Mediterranean in History. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-33)
    Condition: Spine and dust cover are damaged, but book is still usable.
  - Butcher, Kevin. Roman Syria and the Near East. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-26)
  - Carroll, Maureen. Earthly Paradises: Ancient Gardens in History and Archaeology. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-16)
  - Clark, Gregory T. The Spitz Master: A Parisian Book of Hours. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - Conti, Flavio. A Profile of Ancient Rome. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-16)
  - Corbishley, Mike. Illustrated Encyclopedia of Ancient Rome. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-04)
  - Dalby, Andrew. Bacchus: A Biography. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-16)
    Condition: Front cover deeply creased but intact.
  - De Carolis, Ernesto, and Giovanni Patricelli. Vesuvius, A.D. 79: The Destruction of Pompeii and Herculaneum. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - DeLorme, Eleanor P. Josephine and the Arts of the Empire. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-16)
  - Du Bouchet, Paule, and Fabian Negrin. Prince Orpheus. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-16)
  - Duggan, Jim. Plants in the Getty's Central Garden. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-32)
  - Ford, Colin. Julia Margaret Cameron: A Critical Biography. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-17)
  - Getty, J. Paul. As I See It: The Autobiography of J. Paul Getty. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - Giorgi, Rosa. Saints in Art. Translated by Thomas Michael Hartmann. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 1987.IA.04-19)
  - Gousseff, Catherine, and Fabian Negrin. The Perfect Knight. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-16)
  - Grossman, Janet Burnett, Jerry Podany, and Marion True, eds. History of Restoration of Ancient Stone Sculptures. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - Grossman, Janet Burnett. Looking at: Greek and Roman Sculpture in Stone: A Guide to Terms, Styles, and Techniques. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-04)
  - Hendrix, Lee, and Thea Vignan-Wilberg. The Art of the Pen: Calligraphy from the Court of the Emperor Rudolf II. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-16)
  - Hudson, Christopher, and Anne Lucke, eds. Julia Margaret Cameron: The Complete Photographs. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-26)
  - Holtman, Mollie, ed. Masterpieces of Painting: in the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-04)
  - Impelluso, Lucia. Gods and Heroes in Art. Translated by Thomas Michael Hartman. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2009.IA.01-02)
  - Jacobelli, Luciana. Gladiators at Pompeii. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-16)
  - Karakasi, Katerina. Archaic Korai. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-33)
  - Kren, Thomas, and Scot McKendrick. Illuminating the Renaissance: The Triumph of Flemish Manuscript Painting in Europe. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-16)
    This version issued concurrent with a same-named exhibition in Los Angeles and London. Cover is Simon Bening and Antonio de Holanda, "Genealogical Tree of the Kings of Aragon." Same content as other copy with different cover.
  - Kren, Thomas, and Scot McKendrick. Illuminating the Renaissance: The Triumph of Flemish Manuscript Painting in Europe. Los Angeles, London: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-16)
    This version issued concurrent with a same-named exhibition in Los Angeles and London. Cover not named, mother and child in crowd of women. Same content as other copy, different cover.
  - Le Roy, Pierre. Statuts et Privileges du Corps des Marchands Orfevres-Joyailliers de la Ville de Paris. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - Lyden, Anne. M. Railroad Vision: Photography, Travel, and Perception. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-22)
  - Rowlands, Eliot W. Masaccio: Saint Andrew and the Pisa Altarpiece. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-32)
    Series: Getty Museum Studies in Art.
  - Staccioli, Romolo, Augusto. The Roads of the Romans. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - Walsh, John, ed. Bill Viola: The Passions: A Conversation between Hans Belting and Bill Viola. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-23)
  - Zuffi, Stefano. Gospel Figures in Art. Translated by Thomas Michael Hartmann. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-15)
  - Zuffi, Stefano, ed. Old Testament Figures in Art. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - Armstrong, Carol. Cezanne in the Studio: Still Life in Watercolors. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 1987.IA.04-11)
  - Belozerskaya, Marina, and Kenneth Lapatin. Ancient Greece: Art, Architecture and History. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-16)
  - Borrelli, Federica, and Maria Christina Targia. The Etruscans: Art, Architecture, and History. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - Bowe, Patrick. Gardens of the Roman World. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 1987.IA.04-11)
  - Camporeale, Giovannangelo. The Etruscans Outside Etruria. Los Angeles. 2004. (Box 1987.IA.04-11)
  - Close To Home: An American Album / with an essay by D.J. Waldie. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 1987.IA.04-11)
  - Cox, Julian. Spirit into Matter: The Photographs of Edmund Teske. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-17)
  - Curry, Jane Louise. Brave Cloelia. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 1987.IA.04-11)
  - Curry, Jane Louise. Brave Cloelia. (Signed by author.) Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-22)
    Signed by author.
  - Della Portella, Ivana, ed. The Appian Way: From its Foundation to the Middle Ages. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - Draguet, Michel. Fernand Khnopff: Portrait of Jeanne Kéfer. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-16)
  - Hess, Catherine, ed. The Arts of Fire: Islamic Influences on Glass and Ceramics of the Italian Renaissance. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - Impelluso, Lucia. Nature and its Symbols. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 1987.IA.04-11)
  - Lydakis, Stelios. Ancient Greek Painting and its Echoes in Later Art. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 1987.IA.04-11)
  - Mazzoleni, Donatella. Domus: Wall Painting in the Roam House. Los Angeles. 2004. (Box 1987.IA.04-11)
  - Naef, Weston. Photographers of Genius at the Getty. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-17)
  - Rao, Sirish & Gita Wolf. Oedipus The King. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 1987.IA.04-11)
  - Spivey, Nigel & Michael Squire. Panorama of the Classical World. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 1987.IA.04-11)
  - Stafford, Emma. Life, Myth and Art in Ancient Greece. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 1987.IA.04-11)
  - Strazzulla, M.J. Ancient Lebanon. Vision S.r.l, Rome: 2004. (Box 2006.IA.01-03)
  - Valavanis, Panos. Games and Sanctuaries in Ancient Greece. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 1987.IA.04-11)
  - Williams, Jonathan & Clive Cheesman. Classical Love Poetry. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 1987.IA.04-11)
  - Woff, Richard. A Pocket Dictionary of Ancient Greek Heroes and Heroines. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - Zarabouka, Sofia. Jason and the Golden Fleece. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 1987.IA.04-11)
  - Zarabouka, Sofia. The Story of Alexander the Great. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 1987.IA.04-11)
  - Abbott, Brett. Edward Weston: Photographs from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Allan, Tony. Life, Myth and Art in Ancient Rome. Los Angeles. 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Bagnall, R.S. & D. W. Rathbone. Egypt from Alexander to the Early Christians. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Battistini, Matilde. Symbols and Allegories in Art. Los Angeles. 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Belozerskaya, Marina. Luxury Arts of the Renaissance. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-18)
  - Biris, Manos & Maro Kardamitsi-Adami. Neoclassical Architecture in Greece. Translated by David Hardy. Los Angeles. 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Burn, Lucilla. Hellenistic Art from Alexander the Great to Augustus. Los Angeles. 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Cherry, John. Medieval Love Poetry. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-19)
  - Dalby, Andrew. Venus: A Biography. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Fay-Sallois, Fanny. A Treasury of Hours. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Gerster, G. The Past from Above: Aerial Views of Archaeological Sites. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Giorgi, Rosa. Angels and Demons in Art. Translated by Rosanna M. Giammanco Frongia. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-19)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Thesaurus Cultus et Rituum Antiquorum IV: Cult Places Representations of Cult Places. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 2006.IA.01-02)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed.Thesaurus Cultus et Rituum Antiquorum V: Personnel of Cult, Cult Instruments. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 2006.IA.01-02)
  - Guide to the Getty Villa. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - Harris, John, and Calef Brown. Pop-Up Aesop. Los Angeles, 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-18)
  - Harris, John. Strong Stuff: Herakles and his Labors. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Heseltine, John. Roads to Rome. Los Angeles, 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-19)
  - Hess, Catherine & Karol Wight. Looking at Glass. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Keller, Judith. Milton Rogovin: The Mining Photographs. Los Angeles, 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-18)
  - Keller, Judith. Weegee: Photographs from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-18)
  - Kolb, Arianne Faber. Jan Brueghel the Elder: The Entry of the Animals into Noah's Ark. Los Angeles. 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Kren, Thomas & Kurt Barstow. Italian Illuminated Manuscripts. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Kren, Thomas, Mark Evans, Janet Backhouse, and Nancy Turner. A Masterpiece Reconstructed: The Hours of Louis XII. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-18)
  - Lapatin, Kenneth. Seeing the Getty Villa. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 2006.IA.01-01)
  - Leben, Ulrich. Object Design in the Age of Enlightenment. Los Angeles. 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Lewin, A. The Archaeology of Ancient Judea and Palestine. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Lyden, Anne M. Paul Strand: Photographs from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Lyons, Claire L., John K. Papadopoulos, Lindsey S. Stewart, and Andrerw Szegedy-Maszak. Antiquity and Photography: Early Views of Ancient Mediterranean Sites. Los Angeles, 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-18)
  - Mattusch, Carol C. The Villa Dei Papiri at Herculaneum. Los Angeles. 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Messineo, Gaetano, and Emanuela Borgia. Ancient Sicily: Monuments Past & Present. Rome: 2005. (Box 2006.IA.01-03)
  - Parkin, Tim, Shulamith Shahar, Marcia Pointon, Thomas Cole, and Deborah Cherry. A History of Old Age. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-19)
  - Rao, Sirish & Gita Wolf. Euripides' The Bacchae. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Ridderbo, Bernhard. Early Netherlandish Paintings. Los Angeles. 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)